[bright flute music]
- [Hiraku Voiceover] Let me tell
you a story about a slime.
One day, the slime that
Tia brought here to
purify our waste water and
sewage started to multiply
and now there are lots of
different types of slimes.
They were all harmless,
so I didn't really notice that
they'd been multiplying, but...
[girls gasping]
[dramatic music]
[slime farting]
[slime babbling]
- [Tia] Did it drink
an entire barrel?
- A single slime drank it all?
- My dad can only drink
half a barrel at most.
- That wine was
everyone's property!
- [Lastismoon] You can't go and
drink it without our permission!
- This deserves punishment!
- [Tia] That's right!
- [Lastismoon] Yeah!
- [Sena] Please wait
a minute, everyone!
Let's all calm down!
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
This came as a big shock
to all the alcohol-loving
residents here.
And so began our
village's first trial.
[slime babbling]
- Wait! Let's not!
- Leave it to me!
- Guilty.
- But, Anne!
Oh dear!
- Wait!
- Are we blowing something up?
- I feel bad for it,
so let's move away from
the barbaric options.
How about short
confinement instead?
- [Tia] But that was our
precious alcohol!
[slime farting]
- [Tia] Jeez, this kind
of stuff happens
because you're too soft!
- Pardon?
We're talking about
a slime here.
Even if we punish it,
I'm not sure it's going to
reflect on its action.
- [Tia] Well, you have a point.
- [Lastismoon] It is
a slime, after all.
- [Hiraku Voiceover] And so,
that slime was acquitted.
After that, it began to
pop up during our feasts
and celebrations so that
it could join us.
Oh well. I think it's all right
if we have one slime like that.
Too many would be
a problem, though.
["Flower Ring" by Shino Shimoji
and Aya Suzaki plays]
[bright violin music]
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
The season is autumn.
The summers here aren't
particularly hot or anything,
but it's still nice when
things cool down a bit
and we can get some
more work done.
And here's the result.
[stomach growling]
- I'm so hungry.
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
Autumn means eating.
[Flowrem giggling]
- [Flowrem] There's nothing
like a good hot pot!
It's so tasty!
- Would you stop taking
all the meat, Lasty?
- I'm eating vegetables, too!
[Sena slurping]
- Yummy!
We didn't have these
types of mushrooms
in Howling Village.
- Man, I really love
a good hot pot.
If we could get seafood here,
I bet these would taste
even better.
[girls gasping]
- So what exactly
are you referring to
when you say seafood?
- Let's see.
Stuff like cod, crabs,
or monkfish.
We can make broth from kombu!
Then make a chanco miso hotpot!
- Start researching immediately!
- I've got some info here!
- Oh no!
What do I do?
I've never even seen the ocean.
- Did you say crabs?
Can you eat those?
They're really hard.
- Kombu.
It sounds like something
quite terrifying.
[kombu growling]
- A broth?
That's the soup thing
you showed me
how to make earlier, right?
- That's right.
- Is chanco a kind
of fish, then?
- If we need the ocean,
there's a port city
within the Demonic Kingdom.
You're able to reach it
if you head south
from this village.
They do a lot of trading
of ocean products,
so we might be able to find
some of those fish there.
- Okay! I'll fly over
and check it out.
- Wonderful.
I can go with you.
We can ask a merchant
I know for help.
- [Lu] Let's get started
right away!
- [Flora] I'll take care
of the miso!
- They all really like
hotpots, huh?
- [Anne] Indeed.
- [Lastismoon] See you later!
- [Lu] We're counting on you!
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
When it comes to food,
everyone here
gets very motivated.
Well, nothing makes me
happier as a farmer
than seeing them enjoy my food.
[magical music]
And so, the return of the group
that set out in earnest
took place.
Three days later.
- It's a great pleasure
to meet everyone.
My name is Michael.
I'm an established merchant from
the city of Shashato
in the Demonic Kingdom.
- I'm the mayor, Hiraku.
Thank you for coming here
to our little village.
- Of course.
It's nothing, really.
This is part of my job
as a merchant.
[group gasping]
These are the marine
products I brought
from the city of Shashato.
They are our pride and joy.
As for the seaweed called kombu
that you requested,
our fishermen normally
throw it back,
even if they pull up some
in their nets.
- What? So...
- No need to worry
about it, though.
I'll have my men collect some
kombu for you right away.
We'll have it dried and ready
before you know it.
- That sounds great.
- Now with regards to my visit
here to your village today,
I have three main goals.
[Hiraku sighing]
The first is to
properly greet you
and show you
my gratitude for
requesting to do
business with us.
The second is to suggest
more opportunities
for us to trade goods
and do business.
And my third goal,
if it's something
you would agree to,
is to become the official
government purveyor
for this village.
- Official purveyor?
- It means he would
like to handle
all trade between us
and the outside world.
- You're being quite direct
in what you're asking for.
- I'm always careful to not be
so indirect that my intentions
are somehow misinterpreted.
All of the crops here you
have are very enticing.
If you allow me the
opportunity to do so,
I can get you several times
more value when trading them.
- There are quite a few
people already
who want to do trade
with this village.
- As I said, if you agree to it.
Of course, I'd like to ask
that you first have
a look at the
list of products
that my company trades
for other entities.
And from there, we can
discuss my proposition.
I believe we were able to cover
a lot of important ground today.
Next time,
I'd like to discuss
the alcohol produced
in this village.
- [Lastismoon] You can't
have the alcohol!
[Michael screaming]
[Michael coughing]
- Pardon my ignorance.
I'll leave things as is now.
- Well, he seemed like
a skilled merchant.
That should come in handy.
- It certainly will.
- It'll be a big help
having him negotiate.
- And even though he's
handling things for us,
we'll get more goods
when trading now.
- It doesn't seem like he has
any intention to deceive us.
- Yeah.
I hope our relationship
with him goes smoothly.
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
It seemed like he was
really frightened
there at the end.
But oh well.
That's to be expected when
you're talking to a dragon.
[ominous music]
- [Michael] The Great
Tree Village, huh?
[Michael sighing]
[Michael screaming]
- [Michael Voiceover]
That was scary!
[upbeat electronic music]
[seagulls squawking]
[playful music]
- [Michael] A visitor?
Without an appointment?
- Yes. They would like to
talk business with you.
- [Michael] I couldn't be
any busier now.
- [Michael Voiceover]
My name is Michael Goroun.
I work as the head of
the largest
trading company
in this city.
- If it's nothing major,
can't you guys handle it?
Why do they need to
see me specifically?
- The person that
requested you
did so by name
when they arrived.
They even brought goods
from their farm.
I wasn't sure what to do.
- They already brought
goods with them?
Don't they know
the rules here?
If you guys can't
handle it on your own,
then just refer
them somewhere el-
No, I'll meet with them.
- Yes, sir.
- [Michael Voiceover]
My merchant's intuition
is telling me that
I can't ignore this.
This strange feeling
welling up inside me is...
- I feel so very honored
that you remember me still.
- Yes, of course I do.
If I remember correctly,
the last time we had
the pleasure of meeting
was at your birthday party.
- [Michael Voiceover]
I can't believe the young lady
of the Chrome family is here.
My head would've rolled
if I had sent her away.
- Who have you brought with you?
- Oh! My companion is...
- My name is Lastismoon
of the dragons.
Please call me Lasty.
- [Michael Voiceover]
Lastismoon?
Could she really be
that crazy dragon?
She's just a child!
[Lastismoon sighing]
The daughter of
one of the most
powerful families of
the Demonic Kingdom
and a dangerous dragon!
The risks of trading
with them are too high.
- So what is it that brings you
here to see me today?
- [Michael Voiceover]
But I can't just ignore them!
- We'd like you to
purchase these from us.
[Michael gasping]
And in exchange,
there are some things
we'd like you to find.
[Michael gasping]
- [Michael Voiceover]
What's going on here?
I'm being stared down
by a dragon
while being surrounded
by lizardmen.
I'm about to enter some
outrageous trade talks.
Was that feeling I had before
a warning of impending danger?
[Michael inhaling]
[Michael gasping]
These are those fruit
that have entered
the Demonic Kingdom
that people have
been talking about!
Each one of these can fetch
several silver coins!
And look how many
they've brought!
[coins rattling]
- [Michael] The goods you wanted
were from the ocean, correct?
- That's right!
- This port happens
to be my territory.
I can find whatever it is
you are looking for.
[girls gasping]
Because that's...
the job of a worthy
merchant like me!
- [Michael Voiceover] I can't
let this chance get away.
- I want you to go to the port
and bring me their best catches!
- Okay!
- And after that, prepare
my things for travel!
- [Employee] Yes, sir!
- I'll take part in
the delivery myself.
Are the goods
going to the capital?
- Actually, they're
going to a village
in The Forest of Death.
- I'll carry the stuff,
so I can give you
a ride as well.
- [Michael Voiceover]
Forest of Death?
Give me a ride?
[Michael screaming]
- He's a merchant from Shashato.
- I see.
[Michael screaming]
- Oh.
And the merchant came with you?
[Michael growling]
- [Michael Voiceover]
The mayor seems normal.
[Michael gasping]
- [Lastismoon] You can't
have the alcohol!
[Michael trembling]
[upbeat folk music]
[Michael sighing]
- [Michael Voiceover]
I survived it.
I managed to finish my business
with that terrifying group
while having a smile on my face.
That was the best deal
of my life.
Huge profits are waiting for me
from here on out.
[Michael sighing]
However...
[stomach grumbling]
[Michael groaning]
I'm not sure if my body
can handle this.
[girls gasping]
[Hiraku humming]
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
Here it is, real seafood!
Maybe next time I'll ask him
for shrimp or squid!
[girls giggling]
[bright folk music]
[banging]
[dragon growling]
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
This is the third time a dragon
has attacked this village.
I think.
Is this one related
to Dryme again?
For the record,
the three angel squad
in charge of
patrolling the skies
was quickly able to
spot this dragon
before it fully reached us.
However, stopping a dragon
proved to be difficult.
But seriously,
what is that dragon doing?
Acting smug?
[fireball exploding]
[Hiraku groaning]
Okay, so you're challenging me.
You want a fight, right?
In that case...
I missed!
Is what I want it to think.
Once more!
Defeated!
[crash]
[wolves barking]
[Hiraku groaning]
- Ow, ow, ow!
Aw, you got me
with that spear.
I surrender!
Just kidding.
[chuckling]
- Why'd you do
something like that?
- Well, you see, it really isn't
all that big of an issue.
- But you burned
some of the forest.
- Okay. Give me a minute.
I'll come up with an important
reason why I did that.
[Hiraku growling]
- Hey!
Wait a minute, mayor!
I'm sorry, mayor, she's...
[Hakuren gasping]
- It's little Drymey!
- [Hiraku] Little?
- [Hiraku Voiceover] According
to Dryme's explanation,
her name is Hakuren.
She's his older sister.
- This is your fault,
you know, Drymey.
You said you were giving away
Lasty as a bride-to-be.
- As a bride?
- No, that's not what I-
- You totally said that!
You said you wanted
to marry her off
to the mayor of
this village someday.
- Wait, what?
- It's not like that!
I might've said something
kind of like that
while I was drinking, but...
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
As the person in question,
it makes it hard to comment.
- So that's why I came out here,
to see what kind of person he
was marrying my niece off to!
- Then why couldn't you just
come visit like normal?
- Everyone always talks about
how strong the mayor here is.
So I wanted to come
play with you a little.
[Hiraku growling]
- It's not just that, though.
She's mostly here to vent anger.
- Of course I am!
Do you think I could
just let it slide
that my little niece
is going to
find a husband
before I do?
I mean, come on!
She's 900 years
younger than me!
I can't accept this!
It's ridiculous!
Don't you agree?
- It's fine if you
wanna come play,
but you shouldn't be causing
problems for other people.
And it goes without saying that
you're going to clean up
this mess, right?
- [Hakuren] So you two
are always getting
to eat food that
tastes this good?
- Well, it's not like I'm always
imposing on everyone here.
Only three out of
every ten days.
- Oh wow!
Lucky you!
- Maybe it's five days.
- She's already fitting in.
- [Hakuren] Five days?
- Mayor.
I'm sorry about what happened
and that my aunt is...
- [Hakuren] Hey, Lasty!
- That Big Sis Hakuren
is causing so much trouble.
- It's nothing you need
to apologize about.
- Oh, hey!
I heard you have some really
fun games you all play.
Like the one where you line up
the little square things.
- Do you mean mahjong?
- [Hakuren] I wanna try that.
You play with
four people, right?
Hey, mayor!
Let's play a round!
I don't wanna leave here
only having lost to you.
- All right, that's fine by me.
So, first, let me
explain all the rules.
- I'll be fine!
I can figure it out.
- Is that so?
- More importantly...
what should we bet on?
- Huh?
[Dryme chuckling]
- I see, then.
Yes, doing it this way
is more fun than
just playing the game.
- Let's take it easy at first.
- Mayor.
What would you normally bet
when playing mahjong like this?
- Even if want me
to bet something,
I don't really have
anything I can safely bet.
Maybe punish the loser?
The only thing
I can think to do
is play strip mahjong.
[Hakuren squealing]
- Sounds great!
- So the loser gets a
taste of humiliation, then.
- No, no! Don't do anything
you don't want to do!
Right, Lasty?
- If we're competing,
there's no way I can lose.
- [Hiraku] Excuse me?
- [Group] As a member
of the dragon clan!
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
I have a feeling
that things are
going to get bad.
- That's chii!
[Dryme gasping]
- That's riichi!
- Too bad.
Ron!
- [Dryme] What?
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
This is my fault
for carelessly
suggesting this idea.
[Dryme grunting]
- This is indeed
a very shameful thing.
- [Hiraku Voiceover] The dragons
are all very competitive
and they can't stand losing.
This lead to a very serious
game of strip mahjong.
You're new to this,
aren't you?
And you're wearing
the least clothing.
How are you so confident?
Now that it's come to this,
I wanted to carefully rack up
some points and end things
while maintaining the peace,
but...
[suspenseful music]
Something isn't right.
Seriously,
what's happening here?
How am I losing?
I'm on my last
piece of clothing!
Don't tell me they're using
some kind of magic trickery!
Are they using telekinesis
to rewrite the tiles?
Can they see through
the back of my tiles?
No.
- Nothing's written on this one.
Is it an extra?
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
I'm overthinking it.
In any case...
my chance has finally arrived.
I can score a double yakuman.
I can end the whole thing
with a single move.
But...
Of course it had to be
this tile again!
It doesn't matter.
I'll never beat the dragons
if I'm paralyzed by fear!
- [Group] Ron!
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
That's about right.
- Okay, pants off!
- [Girls] Pants off!
Pants off!
[Lastismoon gasping]
Pants off! Pants off!
[girls squealing]
- [Hiraku] I am defeated!
- [Grattz] The dragons
are gathering
in that village again?
- Yes.
The ancient dragon Hakuren
was spotted
staying there as well.
- Impossible.
They've got enough power
to conquer a whole country!
Can we afford to just
sit back and watch?
- So, more importantly,
Beezel...
- Yes?
Do you have an idea, Galgardo?
- No.
It's my daughter.
She's been in a mood lately.
She hasn't said
anything to me all day
besides good morning.
Is this her rebellious phase?
- Anyways, we need to focus on
preparing our military forces!
We'll have to secure
the funds we need.
- [Randan Voiceover]
I resign. Randan.
- [Grattz] Randan?
- [Beezel] Ah, he ran away.
- [Grattz] Is this a joke?
- So, if you divide these apples
between three people,
how many apples will
you have to eat, then?
I wish I could just
eat them all, though.
[class laughing]
- She's really come
into her own here.
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
After attacking
The Great Tree Village,
Hakuren decided to stay here
for the time being.
Surprisingly, she's very skilled
and able to handle any job.
But she complains about
anything she's asked to do.
Every time I look,
she's doing nothing.
- I don't wanna.
- Why do you complain about
everything so much?
- I'm hoping that one day,
maybe people will stop
asking me to do things.
[Hiraku sighing]
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
I had no choice
but to order her
to start digging holes
and then filling
them back in.
- Stop being so cruel!
- She gave up on day one.
- [Hiraku Voiceover] In the end,
we settled on her teaching
reading, writing, and math.
She became the village teacher.
- And that's why
learning to read, write,
and do math will
end up helping you
a lot in your day
to day lives.
Listen up.
I want all of you
to work really hard
so that one day I don't have
to work anymore, okay?
- [Class] Okay!
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
I think her motivation
might not be the greatest.
- Please, we beg of you
to spare our lives.
- What are you talking about?
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
According to what
the lamia girls were saying,
at some point, the
younger animals decided to
clear a dungeon they found
in the middle of the forest,
forcing the lamia to
quickly flee their homes.
[lamia gasping]
[wolves barking]
They didn't know
what they were doing,
but they still caused
a lot of trouble.
- What should we do?
- They came all the way here
to seek our aid and protection
from having lost their homes.
It would not be proper
to turn them away.
- [Hiraku Voiceover] In the end,
we decided to trade
the precious gems
the lamia mined
for some of our crops.
After that, they went back
to their original homes.
- I'd like it if we could
keep trading from now on.
- Yes!
Just ask us for
whatever you want.
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
They're so genuinely
excited about this
that it's making me awkward.
- Okay, then, I have something
I'd like to request.
- [Junea] Yes?
- It's fine if it's only
when you're visiting,
but I'd appreciate it if you
could put some clothes on.
[dreamy music]
- [Hiraku Voiceover] That might
be part of their culture,
but I really had trouble
not staring.
After that, the lamia formed
the Lamia Delivery Service
and started carrying our
trading goods for us.
With everything said and done,
I'm glad we found
some reliable neighbors.
Between this and the increased
trade with the other areas,
it feels like the village
has reached a new level.
- Since we've increased
the amount of trade,
shall we plant more crops?
- Yeah.
[bright folk music]
[ominous music]
- It appears that village is
indeed amassing military might
and planning something
most dreadful.
- It may be that they're
convincing Flowrem to stay there
just so they can use her as
a hostage if they need to.
- We should begin gathering
our troops at once,
Princess.
- I understand.
We must defeat that village.
And we have to save Flowrem.
["Feel the winds"
by Yui Hizuki plays]
[rustic music playing]